basegear.com 2003-06-22

# Privacy Policy

_This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the[Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information._

 **BaseGear.com Privacy Policy**

BaseGear.com takes your privacy seriously. We respect your right to privacy and your desire to enjoy a secure online shopping experience. We have developed this privacy policy in order to inform you of our privacy practices. As part of Yahoo! Store, we strictly adhere to the privacy guidelines adopted by Yahoo! as detailed above. We have adopted the following additional policies to further protect your privacy rights.

**Information We Collect**

When you purchase a product on BaseGear.com, we ask for your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and credit card information. This information is used to process and to fill your order. All information we collect from you is stored in a secure Yahoo! Store database. 

**Information Policy**

We never make your personal information or e-mail address available to any other company or organization without your permission.

**About Children**

For their protection, we ask that children not submit any information to us without the consent of a parent or guardian.

**About Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data that a Web server gives to a Web browser. When the same browser asks the server for another page, it includes the cookie with the request. This lets the server know when a sequence of clicks all come from the same browser. And that is 

_all_

cookies do. Using cookies does not give the server 

_any_

personal information about the person visiting the Web site.

Yahoo! Store uses cookies to keep track of each shopper's shopping cart. When a shopper arrives at a store, Yahoo! Store assigns that shopper a unique cookie. When the shopper clicks on an Order button, we use the cookie to decide what shopping cart to put the product into.

Without using cookie technology, there is simply no way to make a shopping cart work. For example, unless the Web server has some way to tell that two clicks on the Order button are coming from the same browser, it has no way to know that both orders should go into the same shopping cart.

Yahoo! does not store any information in the cookies themselves. The cookies are simply ids. Any information that a shopper enters when placing an order is kept on Yahoo's secure servers. The id in the cookie is merely a key.

To learn more about cookies, please see Netscape's document entitled Cookies and Privacy or their technical specification for cookies if you would like a more in-depth treatment.

**About Security**

All online transactions at Yahoo! Stores are handled with industry-standard 128-bit SSL encryption.

When you enter your credit card number into the order form, it is transmitted across the Internet in an encrypted (scrambled) form, then decoded when it gets to Yahoo!.

For added security, Yahoo! also encrypts the credit card number when it is stored on disk, and when Yahoo! forwards it to BaseGear.com. In addition, your credit card number is permanently deleted from our database 30 days after the date you place your order. (We retain credit card numbers for 30 days in order to process any refunds, credits or exchanges.)

According to CNN, "The prevalent opinion...is that on-line credit card use is actually no riskier for consumers than traditional 'low-tech' transactions."

**Notification of Changes**

If we decide to make changes to our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

If, however, we intend to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection, we will notify users by email and/or by posting a notice on our Web Site for 30 days.

**Contact Information**

Base Gear Company  
255 S Grand Ave Ste 815  
Los Angeles, CA 90012-3038
